{
  "name": "",
  "isFavorite": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Carrot",
      "back": "Havuç"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Potato",
      "back": "Patates"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tomato",
      "back": "Domates"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cucumber",
      "back": "Salatalık"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Lettuce",
      "back": "Marul"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Spinach",
      "back": "Ispanak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Onion",
      "back": "Soğan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Garlic",
      "back": "Sarımsak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pepper",
      "back": "Biber"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Broccoli",
      "back": "Brokoli"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cauliflower",
      "back": "Karnabahar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Eggplant",
      "back": "Patlıcan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Zucchini",
      "back": "Kabak"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mushroom",
      "back": "Mantar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Green bean",
      "back": "Yeşil fasulye"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pea",
      "back": "Bezelye"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Corn",
      "back": "Mısır"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pumpkin",
      "back": "Balkabağı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Radish",
      "back": "Turp"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Celery",
      "back": "Kereviz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Leek",
      "back": "Pırasa"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Artichoke",
      "back": "Enginar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Asparagus",
      "back": "Kuşkonmaz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Beetroot",
      "back": "Pancar"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Chili",
      "back": "Acı biber"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Turnip",
      "back": "Şalgam"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cabbage",
      "back": "Lahana"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Brussels sprout",
      "back": "Brüksel lahanası"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Okra",
      "back": "Bamya"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Parsley",
      "back": "Maydanoz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Dill",
      "back": "Dereotu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Coriander",
      "back": "Kişniş"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Basil",
      "back": "Fesleğen"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Thyme",
      "back": "Kekik"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rosemary",
      "back": "Biberiye"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mint",
      "back": "Nane"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Chives",
      "back": "Frenk soğanı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sweet potato",
      "back": "Tatlı patates"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Yam",
      "back": "Hint yerelması"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Horseradish",
      "back": "Bayır turpu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Scallion",
      "back": "Taze soğan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Endive",
      "back": "Hindiba"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mustard greens",
      "back": "Hardal otu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Kale",
      "back": "Kara lahana"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Collard greens",
      "back": "Kollard yeşilliği"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Romaine",
      "back": "Romaine marul"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Seaweed",
      "back": "Deniz yosunu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Watercress",
      "back": "Su teresi"
    }
  ]
}
